Edward C. Blomeyer photographic collection, Inclusive: 1906-1923, Bulk: 1912-1920
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Company: Telephone, 1906-1920; 1
  - Waco, Central Texas, and San Antonio, 1906-1920; 2
    - Telephone Poles, Lines, and Equipment, 1912-1920
      Poles and lines: E.C. Blomeyer's note on the back of the printed version of this photograph states: "Two rural lines with very 'thin' poles." The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-ple-771.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1916, in McLennan County, Texas, or the greater area.
      Equipment: The image shows a Texas Telephone Company repair and storage facility. The digital image is from a scan of a 4 by 3 ¼- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-ple-689.3.tif. Picture by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1917, McLennan County, Texas.
      Poles and lines: This picture shows an example of the antiquated telephone lines that were once in use around McLennan County and central Texas. The digital image is from a scan of a 1 ¾ by 2 ¾- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-ple-952.1.tif. Photo by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1916.
      Equipment: The image shows a Texas Telephone Company repair and storage facility. The digital image is from a scan of a 4 by 3 ¼- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-ple-690.1.tif. Picture by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1917, McLennan County, Texas.
      Poles and lines: E.C. Blomeyer's note on the back of the printed version of this photograph states: "Three rural lines, at a corner." The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-ple-763.1.tif. Photo by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1916, in McLennan County, Texas, or the greater area.
      Poles and lines: E.C. Blomeyer's note on the back of the printed version of this photograph states: "Four rural lines--note the difference in the height of the poles." The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-ple-763.1.tif. Photo by E.C. Blomeyer, August 6, 1917, in McLennan County, Texas, or the greater area.
      Equipment: Shown are large spools of telephone cable or wire in storage for use by the Texas Telephone Company. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-gen-816.6.tif. Photo by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1917, McLennan County, Texas.
      Equipment: The image shows a Texas Telephone Company repair and storage facility. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 4 inch, photo print. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-ple-513.3.tif. Picture by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1917, McLennan County, Texas.
      Equipment: This image shows a Texas Telephone Company repair and storage facility. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-ple-499.1.tif. Photo by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1917, McLennan County, Texas.
      Equipment: The image shows a Texas Telephone Company repair and storage facility. The digital image is taken from a scan of a 6 by 4 inch, photo print. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-ple-513.1.tif. Picture by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1917, McLennan County, Texas.
      Poles and lines: E.C. Blomeyer's note on the back of the printed version of this photograph states: "Four rural lines. Note the forked 'pole' in the distance." The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-ple-807.2.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1917, in McLennan County, Texas, or the greater area.
      Poles and lines: A primitively constructed rural telephone pole serving as a junction point for several lines is shown. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-ple-497.1.tif. Photo by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1916, in McLennan County, Texas, or the greater area.
      Poles and lines: This image shows primitive rural telephone poles; the negative is marked "Wommack Rd. " The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-ple-767.tif. Photo by E.C. Blomeyer, taken on March 18, 1917, in McLennan County, Texas, or the greater area.
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Central Texas: Flood Aftermath 783-3: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-ple-783.3.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 38)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment 499-1: Central Texas: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-ple-499.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 39)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Central Texas, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 40)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment 514-1: Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Central Texas: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-ple-514.1.tif (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 41)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment 689-3: Central Texas: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-ple-689.3.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 42)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment 689-4: Central Texas: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-ple-689.4.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 43)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment 690-1: Central Texas: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-ple-690.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 44)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment 763-2: Central Texas: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-ple-763.2.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 45)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment 500-2: Central Texas: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-ple-500.2.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 46)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment 497-1: Central Texas: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-ple-497.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 47)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment 509-2: Central Texas: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-ple-509.2.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 48)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment 807-2: Central Texas: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-ple-807.2.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 49)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment 757-3: Central Texas: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-ple-757.3.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 50)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment 758-1: Central Texas: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-ple-758.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 51)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment 768-1: Central Texas: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-ple-768.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 52)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment 767: Central Texas: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-ple-767.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 53)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Central Texas: Katy Railroad 795-3: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-ple-795.3.tif, 1918 February 23 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 54)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment 769: Central Texas: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-ple-769.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 55)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Central Texas:, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 56)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment 807-1: Central Texas: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-ple-807.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 57)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment 771-1: Central Texas: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-ple-771.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 58)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment 787-1: Central Texas: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-ple-787.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 59)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment 763-3: Central Texas: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-ple-763.3.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 60)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment 772-1: Central Texas: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-ple-772.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 61)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment 785-3: Central Texas: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-ple-785.3.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 62)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Glen Rose Road 762-3: Central Texas: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-ple-762.3.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 63)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment 763-1: Central Texas: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-ple-763.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 64)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: McGregor Road 757-2: Central Texas: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-ple-757.2.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 65)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Central Texas: McGregor Road, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 66)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Central Texas: McGregor Road, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 67)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Central Texas: McGregor Road, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 68)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Central Texas: McGregor Road, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 69)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Central Texas: McGregor Road, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 70)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Central Texas: McGregor Road, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 71)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Central Texas: McGregor Road, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 72)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Central Texas: McGregor Road, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 73)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Central Texas: Temple Road, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 74)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Central Texas: Grove Road, Moody, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 75)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Central Texas, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 76)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Central Texas, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 77)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Central Texas: Elm Mott, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 78)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Central Texas: Waco, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 79)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Central Texas, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 80)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Central Texas, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 81)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Central Texas: Near Ocee, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 82)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Central Texas, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 83)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Central Texas, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 84)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Central Texas 952-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-ple-952.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 85)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Central Texas, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 86)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Central Texas, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 87)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Central Texas, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 88)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Central Texas, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 89)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Central Texas, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 90)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Waco and Central Texas, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Waco and Central Texas, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Waco and Central Texas, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Waco and Central Texas, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Waco and Central Texas, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Waco and Central Texas, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Poles, Lines, and Equipment: Waco and Central Texas, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - General, 1906-1920
      This subseries shows operators, switchboards, and telephone related scenes. The locations the images were taken are in Texas, Missouri, and Illinois.
      A telephone switchboard is shown at an unknown location. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-gen-509.1.tif. Photo by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1917.
      This flood scene is believed to be in Missouri. The digital image is from a scan of a 4 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-gen-792.4.tif. Photo by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1906.
      A telephone operator at a switchboard is shown at an unknown location. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-gen-510.1.tif. Photo by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1917.
      A telephone operator at a switchboard is shown at an unknown location. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-gen-511.2.tif. Photo by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1917.
      This flood scene is believed to be in Missouri. The digital image is from a scan of a 4 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-gen-775.3.tif. Photo by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1906.
      This image is believed to be of a group touring a power or telephone facility. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-gen-510.2.tif. Photo by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1920.
      Telephone operators at a switchboard are shown at an unknown location. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-gen-923.1.tif. Photo by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1917.
      - General: Flood Scene 809-4: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-gen-809.4.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 91)
      - General: Telephone 792-4: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-gen-792.4.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 92)
      - General: Telephone 775-3: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-gen-775.3.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 93)
      - General: Telephone Poles 511-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-gen-511.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 94)
      - General: Unknown Group 510-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-gen-510.2.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 95)
      - General: Telephone Operator 510-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-gen-510.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 96)
      - General: Telephone Switchboard 509-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-gen-509.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 97)
      - General: Telephone Switchboard, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 98)
      - General: Telephone Poles-Unknown Location 496-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-gen-496.2.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 99)
      - General: Telephone Operator 511-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-gen-511.2.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 100)
      - General: Telephone Operators 923-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-gen-923.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 101)
      - General: Telephone Equipment 816-7: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-gen-816.7.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 102)
      - General: Telephone Equipment 816-6: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-gen-816.6.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 103)
      - General: Telephone Equipment 816-8: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-gen-816.8.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 104)
      - General: Telephone, 1906-1920 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Texas., 1906-1920; 2
  Edward Charles Blomeyer left behind a detailed photographic record of the state during the time he lived in Waco, Texas (1912-1920), after moving from Missouri to work in the telephone business. He photographed Waco extensively, including images of local military facilities, events, parks, rivers, and parades. Around the state, he took pictures on trips to San Antonio, Austin, New Braunfels, Port Arthur, Galveston, and Lake Greenbriar in Tyler. A few of the images pre-date the year E.C. Blomeyer moved to the state, including some of the images of San Antonio which were taken approximately 1906.
  He also photographed the railroad that ran through central Texas including the Missouri Kansas and Texas (MKT) and St. Louis Southwestern Railway (Cotton Belt). These show locomotives, carriages, crossings, and tracks. The rural roadways in and around McLennan County are detailed as Blomeyer took pictures of the rough road conditions encountered in his travels by automobile. Also included is a group of pictures of an unidentified Texas oil field.
  - Waco, 1912-1920; 1
    E.C. Blomeyer lived in Waco, Texas, from 1912-1920. As well as serving as President of The Texas Telephone Company, he was also an avid photographer. His images shown in this subseries show Waco during an important time in its history as it was experiencing tremendous growth with many changes.
    Some images include Rich Field, Camp MacArthur, derailment of Camp MacArthur troop train, Gurley Park auto race, monuments, Texas Cotton Palace Parade, Texas Cotton Palace main building, cotton trade days on the Waco city square, Brazos River, Washington Street Bridge, floods in downtown, and Elm Street.
    - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges, 1912-1920; 1
      This group of images shows some of Waco's most popular scenic spots such as Cameron Park, located within the city and the Brazos and Bosque Rivers that flow through the park and nearby downtown. The river crossings that span the Brazos such as the Waco Suspension Bridge, Interurban Bridge, and the Washington Street Bridge are shown. Images of the Brazos River at flood as well as low water levels are seen. Elm Street is included as the images show how it was adversely affected when the nearby Brazos River flooded.
      This image was taken in Cameron Park, Waco, Texas, with the Brazos River below and the Bosque River in the background. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-cprb-507.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1916.
      The Washington Street Bridge is seen as the Brazos River is at flood level. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-cprb-694.2.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1916.
      This photo shows the entrance to the wooded river trail that goes along the west side of the Brazos, in Cameron Park, Waco, Texas. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-cprb-890.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1916.
      The note on the back of the printed version of this photograph reads: "The dry creek-McLennan County." The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-cprb-803.3.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1916.
      During heavy flooding, the Brazos River would break its banks and overflow onto Elm Street, Waco, Texas, as seen here. The digital image is from a scan of a 4 by 3 ¼- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-txwaco-723.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1913.
      The note on the back of the printed version of this photograph states: "Bosque River-waterfall?" The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-cprb-764.2.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1916, McLennan County.
      E.C. Blomeyer, with his camera, looks down on the Brazos River from one of the cliffs of Cameron Park, Waco, Texas. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-pplblofmly-507.2.tif. It dates to circa 1916.
      The Brazos River near Cameron Park is at high water level as pictured. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-cprb-814.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1916.
      The Brazos River near Cameron Park is at low water level as pictured. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-cprb-815.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1916.
      Looking west on the Waco, Texas, Suspension Bridge toward Bridge Street. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-cprb-810.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1916.
      The Interurban Bridge is seen here from the east side of the Brazos River, Waco, Texas. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-cprb-703.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1916.
      The Washington Street Bridge is seen here from the west side of the Brazos River, Waco, Texas. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-cprb-705.2.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1916.
      During heavy flooding, the Brazos River would break its banks and overflow onto Elm Street, Waco, Texas, as seen here. The digital image is from a scan of a 4 by 3 ¼- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-txwaco-723.2.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1913.
      The Interurban Bridge with a Southern Traction Company car crossing it is seen here from the west side of the Brazos River, Waco, Texas. Flood level water is obvious as it flows just under the bridge. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-cprb-500.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1916.
      Mrs. E.C. (Amma) Blomeyer is seen on one of the bluffs of Cameron Park, Waco, Texas. In the distance, the Amicable (Alico) Building is visible in the city's downtown area. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ½- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-pplblofmly-885.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1916.
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Cameron Park-Bosque River, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:1)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Cameron Park-River View, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:2)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Cameron Park ? Bridge, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:3)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Cameron Park ? Bridge, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:4)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Cameron Park-Wooded Scene, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:5)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Cameron Park-View from east side of river, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:6)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Cameron Park-Unidentified man standing near cliff, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:7)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Cameron Park-Unidentified man standing near cliff 887-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-cprb-887.2.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:8)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Cameron Park-View of Cliffs 904-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-cprb-904.1.tif, 1917 April 8 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:9)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Cameron Park-Unidentified man Standing near cliff 888-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-cprb-888.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:10)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Cameron Park Cliffs 883-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-cprb-883.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:11)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Cameron Park-View from east side of river 805-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-cprb-805.2.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:12)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges. Cameron Park-Unidentified man Standing near cliff 884-1; Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-cprb-884.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:13)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Cameron Park-Entrance to Brazos river trail 890-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-cprb-890.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:14)
      - Cameron Park, Rivers, and Bridges: Cameron Park ?-Main Road, 1906-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:15)